Hello everyone, it's been a while since I've been here, but as you can see, I'm here in Yawata City, and I'm here with an idea and a first.
As you can see, it's been a while since I've been in Yawata City, and I'm here today with an idea and a first time.
The reason I'm here today is because... you're meeting his wife for the first time, right?
She just opened a salon, so she's going to meet my daughter.
I just opened a salon, so I wanted to give my daughter a chance to experience essay writing.
It won't be me.
It's a first meeting with Monoz and his wife.
I'm going to start today.
We're going to talk about dogs and stuff, and then we're going to go out for dinner.
And then we'll go out for dinner.
Let's go.
Okay, bye.
Oh, here's a video.
Oh, a video.
What?
You don't usually walk your dog, do you?
No.
Well, I don't have a needle, so I don't get a chance to touch them.
That's right.
They eat a lot of grass.
Yeah, I mean, this time of year...
The grass is so green, it's like a salad bar.
My dogs are so excited!
And besides, today was the first time they came to our house.
It turned out that he was allergic to the cat.
But I'm still glad he wasn't allergic to dogs.
You know, it's still a mystery to me.
Carl, let's go.
Carl! Carl!
Carl, come here.
I'm coming.
You're eating so much food.
Carl, come here.
Come on, Carl.
I'm coming.
Carl, come here.
Come here. Come here.
Come here, Carl.
He's so cute.
Is Carl turning six this year?
He's six. Can I say his age?
His real age? Yeah, I mean, his real age.
No, I'm not eating. I'm not eating. I'm not eating. Come on, guys.
He really doesn't want to eat.
I'm puking my guts out.
That's right.
But, you know, they're big, so it's hard work.
But you know what?
What's the word...
Reed? Oh, Reed.
It's too big.
I just saw my dog, Carl, over there.
He found the dog over there.
He's chasing after it.
I mean, all he saw was grass.
You're right.
You're fast.
That's nice.
Today...
He even helped me eat.
Really?
Wow, you put it all down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A food stand.
And, you know, everyone knows the order.
I mean, they know exactly where they're going to eat.
Oh, they already know where they're going to eat.
Yeah, Kevin and Carl over here.
You know.
Kaluha's trying to eat everybody else's food.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, don't let them.
Quick!
They're fast.
They're not going to make it. They're not going to make it.
Eat slowly.
Ponies are the slowest.Ponies are the slowest.
Kevin, you know, all day long.
He's been looking at Moa and woofing and woofing.
He's wagging his tail.
He wants me to play with him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my goodness, Kevin.
Okay, let me out.
I'm so happy for you.
Kev, you want some?
Lift me up. I can lift you up.
You just had a little baby.
I'm having one right now, too. Oh?
What?
I can lift it.
Maybe not Chi.
Oh, I think I can get up to a day or a pony or something.
Yeah.
Snake, if you get tongue-fucked.
Kaybin, come here, Kaybin.
Come here, Ah Ching. You're a strong kid.
Yes, very strong.
So, we're at the restaurant... and I thought we'd have yakiniku.
It's been a while. Today we're going to Narita.
Let's have dinner.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's take pictures when the food arrives!
Well, everyone, the meat sushi has arrived! It looks so delicious!
Wow, I've never had caviar before!
This is probably not caviar.
This is a trifle.
It's so cute!
I'm going to draw a big picture of this.
It's cute.
I knew it. Pictures are important.
Oh, you can totally eat it.
Here you go.
Which one do you like?
Okay, here's the truffle.
Bon appétit truffle.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Yes, it's good.
Are you okay?
You can eat it?
Yeah, I can eat it.
Mushrooms.
That's why you don't like them.
They're good!
It's good, but it's not for adults.
I guess you're right.
Okay, you two.
Now that we've got the meat...
Now that we have the meat, let's see...
I'll show you what the meat looks like in another shot.
Let's start eating now.
Let's grill it.
I can cook it with both hands.
The heat is just right.
It's good.
Is it good?
Very tender.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
It's delicious.
Is it good?
Very tasty.
Fleshiness.
Very nice.
This is the category of yukke, salmon roe, sea urchin and caviar.
Let's have it.
Bon appétit!
too good!
One moment.
Yes, it is.
What kind of meat is this?
Beef is beef.
But the yukke is amazing.The yukke is amazing.
Oh, this!
Looks so good!
I had some!
This is yukke, right?
Wow, yukke.
It's in a pile like this.
I've only had it for ages.
Can I mash it up a little?
Go ahead.
What's going on here?
I don't know what to do with it.
Put it in the middle and eat it.
Shall we do that?
You have a doubt? I did.
You know, people who don't usually grill meat on the barbecue, they come to know this one at this time.
Oh, I see. Great.
You don't have to grill it.
Amazing.
That's great. That's great.
Bon appétit!
It's got this flavor.
Is it good? It's delicious.
It's delicious.
Bon appétit.
Yum. Yum.
This octopus part.
It's delicious.
It's a matter of texture.
I'm not sure which is more accurate.
Oh, you like it already?
Oh, yeah.
I think my son
I think she likes it chopped up.
It's delicious.
Oh, yeah?
It's good.
As usual, no one agrees with me.
That's one of the differences between women and men.
That's true.
Maybe it's a little in your face.
No, no, no.
Today.
It's two against one.
We can't win.
What are you talking about?
It's delicious.
You say it's good.
I knew it!
It's good, but...
In terms of texture...
I guess there are different kinds of beauty.
I understand.
But it's...
It's thin and easy to eat.
You can wrap it up.
Next time we go out for yakiniku...
I'm sure I'll remember.
This...
It was my first time today.
I wonder what they were talking about.
I wonder what they're going to talk about.
It's more normal than I thought it would be.
I wonder if I can eat it with the hair of my mouth.
But you know what?
I don't want you to be too self-conscious.
If you're too self-conscious...
I think you might be able to tell.
Really?
I'll try to remember.
You're asking me if it's true.
"Really?" is now "Kengo.
Why Kengo?
I've got an occupational hazard.
Now that you're talking to me normally...
It's like eating.
But, you know, we have kalbi.
We have kalbi, too.
But I was really nervous.
Oh, yeah?Oh, yeah?
No, I'll do that. It's my first time.
We've been together for 10 years, right?
It's our first time.
I'm wondering if there are any bad memories.
I'm worried about that, too.
But you talked about it in a really nice way, so...
That's true.
You were sleeping, right?
I don't know...
I don't know what to write.
When you were focking.
Oh.
I dropped it.
That's right.
I'm an idol.
You know what?
And her face is tiny.
And your face is tiny.
Monsters are tiny.
I'm the smallest.
I'm with you. I'm with you.
It's true.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
It's just recently.
But you know what? Out of the three of us...
I don't think she'd come if she was alone.
-You don't think she'd come?
I know, right?
She wasn't supposed to come the first time.
But now we're having dinner together.
He's training me.
Yoo does a great job with the ribs.
I was used to being in an environment with so many women.
That's right.
I have only female siblings.
Three daughters live here, and the conversation is already
They're so easy to talk to.
They're teenagers, but it's difficult.
Difficult?
I'm lucky.
It's not like they're shy or anything.
It's not really there anymore.
No.
Not that far.
Like you just sank in front of me.
Yeah, I guess.
But...
There was some substance to it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
We'll do anything for you, right?
Women.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm pretty much like...
They're like, "Listen, listen.
Oh, I see.
My family
Oh, thanks.
It's nice to have this kind of distance.
Not at all.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's nice.
Oh, man.
I was so hungry today.
I thought it'd be hard to say even if I was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Mm-hm. - Mm-hm.
The ribs are delicious.
Yes, so...
I ate rice, too.
Thank you for the meal.
We drank a lot after that.
But I've already finished my meal.
Yes, I finished it.
It was delicious.
I'm in a bit of pain, so I can't talk much.
We had a lot of food, and we ate a lot of lentils.We had a lot of food, and we ate a lot of lenglen.
Yes, we did.
You're right.
So maybe another time.
That's exactly what I mean.
I don't mean "another time." I mean...
It's just that...
It's our first time meeting.
Maybe we'll see each other again. Or just the three of us.
Or my sisters.
Or we could take them out.
That's how I'd like to do it.
I'd like to do that.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
That's all for today.
Thank you for your time.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.